Tran Hoang Giang

Front-end Developer



Details

- •
- Tran Hoang Giang
- hoanggiang521999@gmail. com
- 1
- 0362947187
- 335 Cau Giay, Ha Noi
- in linkedin.com/in/ hoanggiang521999
- github.com/ hoanggiang521999

Languages

English

Hobbies

- Play Video Games
- Football
- Coding
- Camping

Objectives

Front-end Developer with 2 years of experience working with language JavaScript, HTML/CSS and many framework/library as AngularJS, Angular2, ReactJS to deliver exceptional customer experiences. Adept at contributing to a highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions, and determining customer satisfaction.

Work Experience

Front-end Developer

Jun 2021 - Present

D2T Software Joint Stock Company, Ha Noi

- Implemented websites, landing pages from concept through deployment
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments
- Collaborated with the UI/UX design teams to improve the website and application
- Outsourced worker MOR Software JSC

Fresher Front-end Developer

May 2019 - May 2021

D2T Software Joint Stock Company, Ha Noi

- Maintained and developed standard feature for the CMS website for the corporation in Viet Nam
- Developed a application with multiple feature for client from Japan using ReactJS
- Find solutions to improve the accessibility and performance application
- Developed REST API for client

Skills

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- Front-end Framework/Library (AngularJS, Angular2, ReactJS)
- Version Control (Git, etc...)
- Agile Methodologies (Scrum)

Education

Engineer In Information Technology

Sep 2017 - Jun 2021

University of Transport and Communications, Ha Noi